Steve Feng

Senior Software Engineer

(156) 0402-4346

baifeng1991321@outlook.com

About Me

Bringing more than 10 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code, creating mockups and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands.

PER SKILLS

Agile Workflow

Programming

Front End Web Development

HTML

CSS

React

Angular

Javascript

UX/UI

Software Best Practices

Web App Development

EDUCATION



2008-09 - 2012-07

Bachelor's Degree

Computer Software Engineering

Shenyang University of Technology - Shenyang, China

EXPERIENCE

2021-07 - Present Lead Software Engineer

Avuxi

- AVUXI created TopPlace[™] the only Plug-n-Play GeoPopularity Engine with worldwide coverage.
- TopPlace™ analyzes geo-tagged BigData from multiple sources to help uncover the social highlights of entire cities and neighbourhoods, instantly highlighting what city areas are popular for what, whom and when.
- This platform does the complex work of tracking, cleaning and analysing socially relevant geo spatial data, to make it very easy for OTA's and Metasearch sites to increase conversions and average booking value, after a very simple and quick Plug-n-Play integration.

2020-08 - Present Backend Developer

Zoar Technology

- Zoar Technology is proud to be a small, boutique agency that focuses on offering mobile development solutions for small businesses and startups.
- The Zoar team have been working together for years, and have been developing apps since... well, since that was a thing people were doing.
- Basically, Zoar Technology has walked the startup path, and knows what goes into building a company from the ground up.
- They are familiar with how small businesses are often working under very tight deadlines and may not be entirely sure what they need in order to meet them.

2020-11 - Present Lead Mobile Developer

FIN Digital

- FIN Digital is a digital development firm. We believe in building digital disruption in the technology industry, so we build a lot of artificial intelligence, mobile applications, bots and IoT technologies.
- We focus on taking what already has happened with technology and exploring how it could be stronger, better, faster, and smarter.
- Our belief is that technology changes our society and because of that we build for the first-year startup all the way to the Fortune 500 company that is looking to change how consumers engage and interact with the marketplace.

| iOS Development | |
|--------------------|----------|
| Marketing Strategy | |
| Integration | Z 1 2 |
| Web Services | |
| Project Managemen | t |
| REST API | K |
| lonic Framework | |
| Flutter | |
| Node.js | |
| MongoDB | |
| MySQL | |
| Firebase | |
| Amazon Web Servic | es |
| Vue.js | |
| Nuxt.js | |
| РНР | 1 |
| Java | |
| Web Hosting | |
| Back-End Web Deve | elopment |
| Typescript | (CH) |

2021-12 - Present Lead Software Engineer

OneMind Technologies

- At OneMind Technologies, we help our clients to transform operational decisions and reveal insights through real-time and multi-domain intelligence.
- A recognized pioneer in the Internet of Things, we have deployments in Europe, the Americas, Asia, and the Middle East. Our intuitive and evolutive solutions are dedicated to Construction projects, Infrastructures, Cities, and Territories.
- The Company is part of Affluence Corporation (AFFU), a group listed on OTC Markets
 Pink. Affluence is a diversified group focusing on innovative Edge Cloud, Internet of
 Things, and 5G enhancing technologies.

2021-11 - 2022-1 Lead Mobile Developer

Riafox Inc

- Riafox is an agile digital agency that creates Mobile Apps, Growth-Driven Design Websites, Inbound Marketing, and more to help your business grow and compete from anywhere. Bottom line: We make complicated tasks simple for the end user through mobile and internet solutions.
- We believe that most companies have yet to enter the digital age or take advantage of what the internet offers. Making that crucial shift allows organizations to become more efficient, productive, profitable, and attractive to their audiences. In essence, the internet liberates and empowers the organization by enabling it to pass those benefits to its team members. Riafox offers companies new to the internet the expertise, experience, and know-how needed to leverage these resources and become a powerful player online.

2020-11 - Present Lead Mobile Developer

DiningCity, Asia

- DiningCity is an online dining platform in Asia, which was launched in 2009 in China.
 Currently running in Shanghai, Beijing, Shenzhen, Guangzhou and Hong Kong.
 DiningCity Greater China started off as a franchise and is now running independently.
 We work with the top restaurants and leading lifestyle brands in China.
- DiningCity Asia is an online dining guide, currently listing over 2.000 restaurants in China & S.E. Asia. DiningCity is also the organizer of successful dining events like Restaurant Week, Elite Dining Week, Brunch Weekend, Rioja Wine & Dine Festival, Riesling Weeks, and more.
- Currently we have operations teams in Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou, Shenzhen,
 Chengdu, Hong Kong and Bangkok.

2020-11 - Present Lead Mobile Developer

DiningCity, Asia

- Practice makes you perfect The mantra behind Perfectice.
- Perfectice is an GLOBAL OPEN platform for assessment (test preparation). A true
 platform to enable, independent teachers, schools, learning centers, coaching
 institutes, corporate (business), online learning platform and publisher to create
 assessment and students to take those test anytime-anywhere.
- The more student practice, more they know about themselves and better they become that's how Perfectice helps you.